[♪ opening theme song playing]
[phone vibrating]
[TACHIKAWA] Hello?
Yeah, I'm at work right now.
Yeah, everything
will be all right.
Hey, Gabby,
why don't we take a break also?
Oh, right, forgot.
She had a job to do.
Oh, wow, you're all by yourself.
Miss Gabby's so protective,
she's normally
stuck to you like glue.
This is a rare sight, isn't it?
How about I stay
to keep you safe?
Hey, Akio?
You look strange.
Are you hiding something?
Akio?
Uh, no, I'm actually fine
by myself.
I said I'm okay.
Hold on. Stop!
'Cause if you get closer...
[man 1 screams]
-[thudding]
-[man 2 screams]
[man 3 panting]
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
This is bad. The Kagemori clan's
head is here!
-[grunts]
-Are you for real?
[man 3 pants]
Yeah! He's going around
smashing up any office
affiliated with Shingo.
By himself!
[ALL] He's what?
[MAN 4] Crap. And you know
he'll have backup!
Natsuki and Fuyuki are always
shadowing him.
They've gotta be nearby!
[MAN 3]
Gonzo's a serious threat,
but Blacklist is scary
in a whole different way!
If they catch us,
they'll wring us
for all the info we have!
[all trembling]
[scoffs]
Though, if we killed Fuyuki
and became
their new master, then...
Right. Whisper's treasure trove
of information
would become ours.
I've got Shingo's bounty ranking
that he sent us.
For Fuyuki's head
and the capture of Blacklist,
-it's 100 million!
-You're kidding me.
Always knew Shingo
was a generous man.
And you know, Fuyuki's daemons
aren't fighters.
We could take them easy.
Maybe, but Natsuki's daemons
are supposed to be tough.
There's no way
they'd be strong enough
to handle all of us
at the same time.
-Wanna try?
-Of course.
Let's go!
[ALL] Yeah!
[MAN 1] Hmm...
I've got eyes
on Natsuki and Fuyuki.
They're on top
of the distro center.
Circle around back!
[monsters growling]
[MAN 1] Kill Fuyuki first.
We need to get Blacklist.
[monsters yelling]
[monsters scream]
[gasps]
[groans]
[all screaming]
[footsteps]
♪
[ASA] Yin, Yang, it's fine.
You can come out now.
[Ohagi and Daifuku exclaiming]
[Akio gasps]
I tried to warn you
to stay away, Akio.
Because now you've
stepped into my reach.
[JIN] Ai, dear?
I don't want you eating
any more of him.
We need him alive to talk.
[Akio sighs]
[AKIO] So when did you
figure me out?
I was suspicious
when we fought Yuru.
Even though I was in charge,
he didn't try
to attack me first.
Not even Haruo, whose daemons
were causing him some trouble.
Instead, he picked the man
who was unarmed and daemon-less.
And went for your head.
That kid, when someone
wants him dead,
he'll respond in his own way.
Yuru got a sense
you wanted to kill him.
And then you bumped off the guy
who led the attack on our manor.
I figured you wanted
to silence him.
So I laid a trap for you,
and here we are.
Want some coffee?
No, thanks. I'm wide awake now.
How'd you know
about the warehouse?
Did your new contact
with Higashi Village
leak that one to you?
There's a shock.
I never thought I'd see the day
when you'd start palling around
with those guys.
[JIN] We're not pals.
[HARUO] Sorry, Akio.
If you're looking
for Asa, she's out.
Even if we don't share blood,
we are still brothers.
I trusted you.
Please don't put up
a fight, okay?
This doesn't have to get worse.
Give up. Beg the master
for your life!
I will be there too.
On my hands and knees!
No point.
You know he's not gonna
forgive me after this.
[Haruo sighs]
[creaking]
[Jin exhales]
[AKIO] But man,
you guys really thought ahead.
Asa's not even
in the manor, huh?
[sighs]
That only leaves me one option.
Turn this whole place to rubble
so she's got
nowhere left to hide.
-[creaking]
-[JIN] Mm?
[AKIO] Mountain God are
far too big of daemons
for Ai to swallow whole.
Not even Haruo's tortoise
can fully shut them down.
I don't think we have a way
to catch the hare,
but elephants don't worry
about flies.
Do you really want to fight me?
You're sure?
[GABBY] Sounds fun.
Let me play.
I'm itchin' for a fight.
[Akio gasps]
[AKIO] No. I saw Gabby
go to the warehouse.
I get it.
They've gotta be bluffing.
It's a daemon.
Tachikawa told us her fox daemon
can transform into people.
It's standing in darkness
to hide its missing shadow.
[Akio gasps]
[GABBY] I can legit see
your mind racing,
trying to figure out how this
whole thing's one big bluff.
Well, stop your thinkin'.
'Cause I got news, you shithead.
We're the real deal!
Wow, what a haul we've got.
Finished down there?
Well done, sir.
Down we go.
Just for now,
I'll take all of them, okay?
Please.
Great. Come on, kids,
meet your new master.
[hums]
♪
Welcome to the family.
I do hope
you'll enjoy your stay.
[monsters exclaiming]
[laughs]
Good! Come to papa!
Aw, there, there!
[Gonzo laughs]
-What the hell?
-Old man took my daemons!
Impossible.
What about their compatibility?
[MAN 2]
That's way too many pairs!
How can he have
such a massive horde
and not deal
with constant infighting?
♪
[NARRATOR]
Gonzo's main daemon pair
is Hyakki Yako.
Compatibility is often
an issue when one attempts
to command multiple
pairs of daemons.
Daemons have minds of their own,
so just like anyone else,
they may or may not
get along with others
when they're forced
into close proximity.
If two contracted pairs
are incompatible,
there may be infighting.
Or worst case, they could bring
harm to their master.
Luckily, that's not
a problem here.
Because there's a daemon pair
made to preserve harmony!
And their name... Hyakki Yako!
There's no need
to worry about compatibility,
because with the help
of these daemons,
Gonzo Kagemori can form
peaceful contracts
with as many pairs as he'd like.
They use Break to make
tons of stray daemons,
then let Gonzo Kagemori
collect them all.
And then with Blacklist,
Fuyuki can extract all of our
information with ease!
[BOTH MEN] Could any combo
be scarier than that?
[SHINGO] What? Break's there?
I knew to expect the clan head,
some Kuroyas, and Gabby.
But nobody mentioned
-Asa coming!
-[YURU] Hm?
Asuma, did you lie to me?
I swear I did not.
I'm surprised, quite.
[Shingo scoffs] Wait.
Where's Ivan?
[YURU] Hmm.
-[SHINGO] Sic him on Gonzo.
-[YURU] Asa showed up, too?
[SHINGO] What? He's not there.
That bastard.
What does he think
I'm paying him for?
[Shingo grunting]
[YURU] I don't wanna see
either of you move.
Take one step towards me,
and your uncle's dead.
[MAN ON PHONE] You still there,
Shingo? Something wrong?
[YURU] I'm gonna borrow
this "smartphone" thing.
Don't mind, do you?
♪
-[Akai groans]
-[AKIO] Now I see.
Makoto Tachikawa's daemon
is the one
who went to the warehouse.
As it turns out,
shapeshifters are always useful.
She opened up options for us.
Moments ago,
I called her pretending
to be a younger brother.
It was really just an excuse
to leave the room.
Luckily,
she's a good actress, too.
And here I was, thinking Asa
had just been left alone
at the perfect time.
I fell for it hook, line,
and sinker.
-[Gabriel growls]
-How unfortunate.
I hate it when women lie.
So you're really goin' through
with this, huh?
Did you forget who it was
that messed up
your daemon's horn, Akio?
[Gabriel growls]
[Gabriel grunts]
[GABBY] Pretty sure I made it
crystal clear
when we first met
which one of us is stronger!
Let's turn this Mountain God
to a patch of dirt, Gabriel.
Jinny! You're on cleanup duty!
I can take care of that.
But you're not to kill Akio
or his daemons.
[Gabby breathes heavily]
I ain't about to make
any promises.
[rumbling]
[objects clattering]
[SERVANT] What's that?
[both talking gibberish]
-[TACHIKAWA] All of you, run!
-[BOTH] Uh?
We need to get out!
-What's going on?
-Is something wrong?
[TACHIKAWA] Orders from Jin!
Get as far away
from Hagure-sensei's annex
as you can!
Spread the word to anyone else
you can find!
-But why?
-[rumbling]
[all gasp]
[SERVANT] Whoa!
Akio let Mountain God come out?
Did assassins
break into the manor again?
They didn't "break in."
-They were already inside.
-Huh?
♪
[TACHIKAWA]
They have been for a while.
[Gabriel growling]
[Yamakaze groans]
[Tanikaze grunting]
[AKIO] Our matchup
against Gabriel is rather poor.
Yamakaze, take out
Miss Gabby first.
Crap!
Hey, Chompers, what you doing?
Don't lose your head
over your enemy.
You've gotta make sure
your master stays safe.
I swear, the two of you always
get too hot and mad.
[Gabriel grunting]
[AKIO] What's he up to?
[Akio grunts]
Tanikaze!
[grunting]
[Tanikaze growling]
[HARUO] Tordy!
[BUNBUN] He couldn't even
slow 'em down!
[Gabriel growls]
[GABBY] Get ready!
Once we've eaten them,
we're comin' for you next!
Leave them alive.
Don't disregard my orders,
Gabby!
Why? They're gonna be dead meat
as soon as the Master
gets home, anyway!
[JIN] At the rate
this fight is going,
Hagure's gonna kill all of us.
[Hagure snores]
[GABBY]
Now, what came out of that
piece of shit mouth earlier?
Something about
turning this place to rubble
so Asa's got
nowhere left to hide? Yeah?
You'll eat those words.
From the moment she was born,
some lousy adults
wanted her dead!
Her own village locked her away
in a cell!
She was cut off from the world
with no chance of freedom.
[Gabriel growling]
[GABBY] Even when
she managed to escape
that disgusting place
with her parents,
people were still trying
to kill her here!
And when she thought she'd found
safety in this manor,
her parents were kidnapped.
She can't even turn
to her grandma anymore!
This is the only place
Asa has left to go!
These walls
don't offer her much,
but at least she has the
teensiest bit of freedom here!
So finally, finally, she's found
somewhere safe
she can live her life.
And you wanna take that away
from her, too?
If you think you're getting away
with that, think again!
[Gabriel growling]
We're done.
[Yamakaze groans]
Yamakaze, Tanikaze,
there's no point in you
going down here with me.
You two should go home.
I'm ending our contract.
[GABBY] They're escaping.
[JIN] Did you forget, Akio?
There's a barrier here.
It goes both ways.
We'll collect them later.
[Akio grunts]
Akio.
[Gabriel growling]
-No, don't!
-Please, Gabby!
-Dummy!
-[GABBY] Gobble.
[Akio gasps]
[Jijimaru and Babamaru
grunting]
[Akio breathes shakily]
[BABAMARU]
Any naughty children about?
[JIJIMARU]
Any crybabies about?
[Gabby grunts]
[NATSUKI] You can't just
kill him, Gabby. Bad girl.
[Gabby grunts]
Don't try to stop me, Natsuki.
[NATSUKI] Cool down.
Asa didn't ask you
to do this for her.
Don't just assume
what she wants.
[Gabby scoffs]
[BABAMARU] Any crybabies about?
Yeah, all right.
Don't gotta tell me twice.
He can walk away
with his life for now.
[Akio gasps]
[JIJIMARU]
Any naughty children about?
[AKIO] Natsuki and Namomihagi
were on deck, too?
You had yourself, Haruo,
Miss Gabby, and Natsuki.
How many people were you willing
to dedicate to fight one guy?
I went all out because I'm aware
of how strong you are.
My job
was to bring you in alive,
and I planned accordingly.
I couldn't afford
to skimp on firepower.
Someone would have died.
I'm honored, sir.
I didn't realize you thought
so highly of me.
[Haruo gasps]
[HARUO] Uh?
Wait, Akio! Come back!
[BABAMARU]
Should we not give chase?
It's fine.
He can't escape.
He's about to learn
there are some fates
worse than death.
[AKIO] They're not pursuing me?
That's weird.
♪
[AKIO] Uh?
Makoto Tachikawa and...
[Midori vocalizing]
[Akio gasps, grunts]
♪
[AKIO] Balls.
[AKIO] This sucks.
[splattering]
-[MAN ON PHONE] Shingo?
-[Shingo grunting]
Are you there? Shingo!
-So, uh, what now?
-Hello?
-Do I just talk into this thing?
-What's happening?
That's right.
Careful not to touch the screen
or you may hang up.
[YURU] Hey, watch those hands.
I said I'd kill him
if you moved.
Sorry, of course.
Though you'd be doing me a favor
if you did kill him.
Huh? What'd you say?
Oh, nothing.
Can you hear me?
You're one of Shingo's guys,
aren't you?
-What? Who's this?
-Me.
"Me" who?
I'm the twin
your boss kidnapped.
It's Yuru from Higashi.
What? How'd that kid get a hold
of Shingo's phone?
[YURU] I've taken
the old man hostage.
His life is literally
in my hands.
What?
[ASUMA]
Spoken like a true villain.
You're gonna release the kids
you're keeping there,
assuming you don't want me
to crush his windpipe.
The hell's your deal?
[Shingo grunts]
No, Shingo!
What are you doing, brat?
I'll kill you!
Sure, fine. You want me dead,
come and get me.
[Shingo grunts]
Jeez. You know,
you're one freaky kid.
Fujin.
[Yuru gasps, grunts]
[YURU] Damn. [grunts]
Raijin.
[Yuru grunting]
I heard you were
a piece of work.
But you're a real savage.
Even with a kid's life
on the line,
you went for the neck.
Now, hey. Let's all relax.
It's not too late
to have a calm chat.
We're actually civilized
down here,
unlike you primitive
mountain folk.
Let's solve this with our words.
[laughs]
Can't tell by looking at me,
but I'm really
a pacifist at heart.
[Yuru breathes shakily]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[YURU] This old guy's daemons
can control lightning and wind!
[SHINGO] Say hi to my daemons,
Fujin and Raijin.
Let's play nice, buddy-boy.